https://drgarbers.com/privacy

Privacy Policy | Dr. Garber's
Shopping Cart
(0)
Your shopping cart is empty!
Call Now: 1-877-374-2723
Free Shipping in the USA
|   Login/Sign Up
My Account
Wish List (0)
Dr. Garber's, LLC, LLC Privacy Policy
It is the policy of Dr. Garber's, LLC, to respect your privacy and the privacy of all visitors to our Web sites. This policy statement has been established to help you understand our commitment to protecting your privacy, and the steps we take to ensure it.
Dr. Garber's, LLC collects certain Personal Information or information that could be used to identify you, such as names, addresses, telephone/fax numbers, or email addresses, when that information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned or otherwise disclosed to anyone outside Dr. Garber's, LLC, our service providers, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. We use this information to answer your requests for information or to better understand and respond to your needs. We never share the information collected at drgarbers.com or maxwellpet.com with third parties for their marketing purposes.
Aggregated Information
Dr. Garber's, LLC may use your personal information to generate Aggregated Information that does not allow you to be personally identified or contacted. Aggregated Information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and may be used by Dr. Garber's, LLC to provide insight on the usage of the services. For example, we might compile personal information in order to determine the percentage of users that live in a particular geographic area.
Tracking Technology ("Cookies")
Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive when you visit a Web site, in order to track use of the site. Some web sites use cookies to collect data regarding the functionality of the site or to help analyze browsing patterns and use of the site.
Dr. Garber's, LLC does not use tracking technology ("cookies") on this site.
Children
Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from using this site. Dr. Garber's, LLC’s sites are not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 18.
Security
The Company recognizes that your privacy is important to you. Dr. Garber's, LLC employs security measures, such as those described below, in order to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of Personal Information under our control.
Technical measures to protect your privacy include, in many instances, the use of passwords and the support of encryption technology in order to ensure the privacy and integrity of your Personal Information, and the secure disposal of Personal Information after it is no longer needed for any business purpose. It is important to recognize, however, that no security measures are perfect, and no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure.
You should take precautions in choosing the information you send to us via email and in keeping your password confidential. You will be solely responsible for all uses of your password, even if such uses were not authorized by you. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password, you are responsible for contacting us to request deactivation of your password.
Information Sharing
Access to your Personal Information is restricted to those employees who require access in order to perform their employment duties. Furthermore, all Company employees are required to abide by this Privacy Policy and are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal, for breach of its provisions.
Dr. Garber's, LLC may share your Personal Information with its affiliates, subsidiaries and service providers for purposes related to: (i) providing the services to you; and (ii) providing you with information about products, services or promotions that may be of interest to you (unless you have opted out of receiving such information). Third-party service providers are also restricted to only that information that is required to fulfill their obligations and required to comply with this Privacy Policy.
Changes to Your Personal Information
We strive to ensure the accuracy of any personal information you provide to us online. If you would like to update or review the personal information we may have on file for you, please email your request at office@drgarbers.com. To assist us in properly updating our files, please include your old and new personal information in your request.
Links to Other Sites
Dr. Garber's, LLC's sites may provide links to sites not covered by this Privacy Policy. Dr. Gar- ber's, LLC is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your Personal Information, so you should check their privacy policies before providing them with such information. Dr. Garber's, LLC does not collect the Personal Information that you provide to these third parties.
Choice
If you do not wish to receive information about our products, visit the Contact Us area of the Web site, where you may opt-out of receiving such information.
Changes
We will remain committed to our underlying goal of protecting your privacy. From time to time, we may update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law or the services that we offer. If we make any material changes to our policy, we will prominently note such changes to this Privacy Policy. Similarly, in the event Dr. Garber's, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its products or assets, your personal information will likely be transferred. We will post any such changes in the control of your personal information to this web page.
You are advised to review this page regularly for any changes.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Dr. Garber's, LLC, or our products or services please contact office@drgarbers.com.
Continue
Information
Ask the Doctor
About Dr. Garber
Testimonials
FAQs
Consult with Dr. Garber
We Support
